...call it 30 degrees, so about half.
(Sheldon:)Exactly half.
(Leonard(snarkily):)Let's push.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Leonard(snarkily):)See, it's moving. This is easy.
It's all in the math.
- What's your formula for the corner?
- What?
(Penny:)Oh, okay.
(Leonard:)Okay, yeah, no problem.
Just come up here, help me pull and turn.
Oh, gravity, thou art a heatless bitch.
(Sheldon:)You do understand
that our efforts here...
(Sheldon:)...will in no way increase the odds of you
having sexual congress with this woman?
(Leonard:)Men do things for women
without expecting sex.
Yeah, those would be men
who just had sex.
I'm doing this to be a good neighbor.
(Leonard:)In any case, there's no way
it could lower the odds.